funquizcards.com 2015-12-26

# Privacy Policy

We respect the privacy of our visitors and surfers. We do not sell or barter email addresses you give us when you register or when you send a quiz. No information is saved regarding the number of quizzes, names or topics of quizzes or their results, which you took on this website. The only information we store is the data which you enter while registering on our website. We do not share this data with anyone else. We reserve the right to use this data to display advertisements or show offers to you which you may be interested in. This we may do in association with third party advertisers. But we give the users the option to pass/skip these advertising offers. If you submit any data in a third party form of any advertiser, please do so only after reading their privacy policy. In any case, we associate ourselves with the best advertisers for the benefit of our users. 

**Limitations on privacy:**  
We reserve the right to provide information if we think - correctly or incorrectly and reasonably or unreasonably - that our quizzes, polls and ecards, are being used in violation of our terms of use, including, but not limited to, being used in any illegal, harmful, threatening or anti-social activity. 

We try to protect your privacy, but you must please understand that any use of the Internet or of email creates the possibility that someone could access the data transmitted. There is always some risk on the web that personal information might be accessed and privacy cannot be guaranteed. 

**Affiliates, Advertisers and Others:**   
Before providing information to any party other than funquizcards.com, you should check their privacy policy, as they are third parties. We may use third party TAF services for the function of sending pages and ecards. We may also use third party advertising services which may display full page ads in between your surfing experience. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices utilized by any other sites or advertisers linked by us. Please read their terms of service and privacy policy before entering any data there. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

For any queries, contact us.
